{
    "subject": "resource/Choricarpia",
    "predicate": "ontology/abstract",
    "object": "Choricarpia is a genus of trees comprising two species endemic to New South Wales and Queensland in Australia:Choricarpia leptopetala, Brown Myrtle or Brush TurpentineChoricarpia subargentea, Giant Ironwood or Ironwood Box\u2191",
    "human_readable": "Choricarpia is a genus of trees comprising two species endemic to New South Wales and Queensland in Australia: Choricarpia leptopetala, known as Brown Myrtle or Brush Turpentine, and Choricarpia subargentea, also known as Giant Ironwood or Ironwood Box.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9234117269515991,
            "question": "What are the two species of Choricarpia trees?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8733777403831482,
            "question": "What type of tree is Choricarpia leptopetala?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8457861542701721,
            "question": "What is another name for Choricarpia leptopetala?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8352817296981812,
            "question": "How many species of trees are in the Choricarpia genus?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7982057929039001,
            "question": "Are there any species of Choricarpia found outside of Australia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7971464395523071,
            "question": "Is Choricarpia a genus of flowering plants?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7940901517868042,
            "question": "Where are Choricarpia trees found?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7854306101799011,
            "question": "What is another name for Choricarpia subargentea?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7399810552597046,
            "question": "Which Australian states are home to Choricarpia trees?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7160971164703369,
            "question": "What is the common name for Giant Ironwood or Ironwood Box?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Choricarpia is a genus of trees comprising two species endemic to New South Wales and Queensland in Australia: Choricarpia leptopetala, known as Brown Myrtle or Brush Turpentine, and Choricarpia subargentea, also known as Giant Ironwood or Ironwood Box.",
            "html": "dbpedia_555_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which Australian states are home to Choricarpia trees?",
            "html": "dbpedia_555_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is another name for Choricarpia subargentea?",
            "html": "dbpedia_555_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where are Choricarpia trees found?",
            "html": "dbpedia_555_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_555_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_555_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_555_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_555_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_555_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_555_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_555_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_555_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_555_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_555_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe provided documents support the statement that \"Choricarpia is a genus of trees comprising two species endemic to New South Wales and Queensland in Australia: Choricarpia leptopetala, known as Brown Myrtle or Brush Turpentine, and Choricarpia subargentea, also known as Giant Ironwood or Ironwood Box.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}